infotracer.com 2010-10-11

# Infotracer

## Our Privacy Policy

**Last Update Date:   January 1, 2008**

This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal and non-personal information we collect on this website, how we use such information and to whom and under what circumstances we may disclose it.  By using the Site, you agree to the collection, use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information as described in this Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site.

**Collection of Information**

### Personal Information

We collect personal information from you when you:  (1) register on the Site; (2) subscribe to one of our mailing lists; (3) contact us; and (4) order products and services.  The information we collect includes your name, address, email address, telephone number.  We also store your searches for 60 days, after which time we delete them. If you make a purchase, our service provider ClickBank will collect your payment information.  ClickBank does not share that information with us.

### Non-Personal Information

s As part of the standard operation of the Site, we may collect certain non-personal information from you, including but not limited to your browser type, operating system, IP address and the domain name from which you accessed the Site.  In addition, we may collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the date and time you visit the Site, the areas or pages of the Site that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing the Site, the number of times you return to the Site, your search history and other click-stream data.

### Cookies

We may use cookies to collect the non-personal information described above.  A cookie is a small text file that may be stored on the hard drive of your computer when you access the Site.  We may also use cookies to remember you when you return to the Site.  In addition, our vendor ClickBank may place a cookie on the Site to recognize the website that referred you to the Site.  You are free to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the Site or take full advantage of all of our offerings.  Check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

**Access to Information You Provide to Us**

You may access any personal information you provide to us and correct or modify such information by sending an email with your request to [**support@infotracer.com**](mailto:support@infotracer.com). 

**Use of Information**

We may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes: (1) to fulfill your requests for products and services; (2) to provide you with targeted offers and advertising on the Site; (3) to contact you via email, direct mail and telephone with service updates and information and promotional materials and offers from our company as well as from our subsidiaries, affiliates, marketing partners, advertisers and other third parties; (4) to contact you when necessary; (5) to review Site usage and operations; (6) to address problems with the Site, our business or our products and services; and (7) to protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business. 

**Disclosure of Information**

We may disclose information collected from and about you to the following entities for the following purposes: **** (1) to our related companies, service providers and suppliers, if the disclosure will enable them to fulfill a product or service request or to perform a business, professional or technical support function for us; (2) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of our terms of use or of our rights or the rights of any third party; (3) **** to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; and (4) in the event that our company or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets.  We **** may also sell, rent or lease your personal information to our marketing partners, advertisers or other third parties.  If you would prefer that we not share your personal information with such third parties, please contact us at [**support@infotracer.com**](mailto:support@infotracer.com).

We may disclose aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about site users to third parties. **Security**

We have taken certain physical, electronic, contractual, and managerial steps to safeguard and secure the information we collect from Site visitors. 

### Your Search History security

All information related to searches performed by you is considered confidential and is not shared with any unauthorized individuals. Contents of your search as well as your search details may not be released to any outside agent and will not be used for marketing purposes. Search history details are stored for 60 day period only and will be deleted on the last day of the storage period. 

**Children**

We do not direct the Site to, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from, children under thirteen. 

**Third Party Websites**

The Site may contain links to third-party websites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own.  We are not responsible for the activities and practices that take place on these sites.  Accordingly, we recommend that you review the privacy policy posted on any site that you may access through the Site. 

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may change this privacy policy from time to time.  When we do, we will post the change(s) on our website.  If we change the policy in a material way, we will provide appropriate online notice to you. 

**Contact Us**

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, contact us at [**support@infotracer.com**](mailto:support@infotracer.com).
